electrons build native desktop apps for platforms like Mac OS and Windows using
electrons 只使用 HTML CSS 和 JavaScript 为 Mac OS 和 Windows 等平台构建原生桌面应用程序
nothing but HTML CSS and JavaScript it's a tool behind many popular apps that you
它是许多流行应用程序背后的工具
might be using today like the s code slack and discord just to name a few on
the front end you build UIs just like you would for a browser-based web app
UI就像基于浏览器的 Web 应用程序一样
and you can bring along to our favorite frameworks but an electron you also have
，您可以使用我们最喜欢的框架，但是您还可以
access to note J s and that means you can access low-level API s that you
访问 note J 的电子，这意味着您可以访问
don't normally have access to in a sandbox browser like the file system
通常没有的低级 API 在像文件系统电子这样的沙盒浏览器中访问
electron combines the front end and back end technologies and provides a bunch of
结合了前端和后端技术，并提供了许多
other tools to work with native menus the system tray and so on
其他工具来处理本机菜单系统托盘等等
let's go ahead and build a desktop app now run NPM in it in an empty directory
让我们继续构建一个桌面应用程序现在在其中运行 NPM 在一个空目录
and install electron then create a main.js file and set that as the main
中安装 electron 然后创建一个main.js 文件并将其设置
entry point into your app every electron app has exactly one main process running
为您的应用程序的主要入口点 每个电子应用程序都有一个运行
it manages the lifecycle of your app and opens the windows that the end user will
它的主进程它管理您的应用程序的生命周期并打开 wi 当您的主应用程序准备就绪时，最终用户将
see each window is its own independent render process running with the chromium
看到每个窗口都是其自己的独立渲染进程，该渲染进程与 chromium Web 浏览器一起运行，
web browser when your main app is ready you can start a new render process by
您可以通过实例化浏览器窗口来启动新的渲染进程，
instantiating a browser window until the window to load a regular HTML file it
直到该窗口加载常规 HTML 文件。
will render the HTML CSS and JavaScript but do so in a native window and give
渲染 HTML CSS 和 JavaScript，但在本机窗口中执行此操作并让
you access to low-level api is to build a true desktop experience create an
您访问低级 API 是为了构建真正的桌面体验创建一个
index.html file and put whatever code you want inside of it but notice how i'm
index.html 文件并将您想要的任何代码放入其中，但请注意我是如何
accessing note Global's directly in my HTML that's not something you can do in
直接在我的 HTML 中访问 note Global，这
a normal web browser an electron gives you control over the operating system UI
在普通 Web 浏览器中是无法做到
as well for example add your own icon and controls to the system tray with
just a few lines of code now after you build something awesome you can package
的 在你构建了一些很棒的东西之后，你可以
it for multiple operating systems from a single codebase tools like electron
从一个代码库中为多个操作系统打包它，像电子
packager or forage can handle the entire distribution process for you with a
打包器或草料这样的工具可以为你处理整个分发过程
single command this has been electron in 100 seconds stay tuned for a full
嗯，这已经是100 秒内的电子，请继续关注
electron project in a few days and make sure to hit the like button if you want
几天后的完整电子项目，如果您
to see more short videos like this thanks for watching and I will see you
想观看更多这样的短视频，请确保点击“赞”按钮，谢谢收看，我会
in the next one [Music]
在下一个[ 音乐]